(smooth synthesizer music)
♪ Watching every motion in
my foolish lover's game ♪
♪ On this endless ocean,
finally lovers know no shame ♪
♪ Turning and returning to
some secret place inside ♪
♪ Watching in slow motion
as you turn around and say ♪
♪ Take my breath away ♪
♪ Watching, I keep waiting,
still anticipating love ♪
♪ Never hesitating to
become the fated ones ♪
♪ Turning and returning to
some secret place to hide ♪
♪ Watching in slow motion
as you turn to me and say ♪
♪ My love, take my breath away ♪
♪ Through the hourglass, I saw you ♪
♪ In time, you slipped away ♪
♪ When the mirror crashed, I called you ♪
♪ And turned to hear you say ♪
♪ If only for today ♪
♪ I am unafraid ♪
♪ Take my breath away ♪
(smooth synthesizer music continues)
♪ Watching every motion in
this foolish lover's game ♪
♪ Haunted by the notion somewhere
there's a love in flames ♪
♪ Turning and returning to
some secret place inside ♪
♪ Watching in slow motion
as you turn my way and say ♪
♪ Take my breath away ♪
♪ My love, take my breath away ♪